http://www.oldworldstnick.com/privacy-policy.html

My Studio
Old World St. Nicks | Handmade original and reproduction Santa Dolls & Christmas Decor
Find us on Facebook
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Last Updated: March 1, 2011 Old World St. Nicks ("OWSN" or "We") will take every step we can to ensure your privacy.  Upon collection of personally identifiable information (if you sign up for our email newsletter, if you contact us, or if you purchase an item), we may collect your personal information in order to complete your request or transaction.  This information will never be sold to a third party.  This information is used strictly for the following purposes:-To answer your inquiries-To communicate with you about an order or potential order-To help us learn about your personal shopping taste-To contact you about future sales, promotions, and new products (you may opt out of those emails if you so desire) CookiesThis site does not currently use cookies.  No data is being transmitted from your computer to our network unless you make a purchase or contact us, at which point we only collect the information you provide.In sum, we treat your personal information as we would want ours treated!  We keep it in-house, and only use it for the most basic of our business functions.
Find us on Facebook
Customer ServicePayment & ShippingRefunds and Exchanges
Our CompanyPrivacy Policy
Email Signup
* Indicates required field
Email *
sign up for our newsletter and be the first to learn about new collections!
Submit
Powered by
Create your own unique website with customizable templates.
Get Started
